http://www.eastearthtrade.com/privacy-policy.aspx

Select ...
Acuzone
Allergy / RespiratoryAromatherapy & Essential OilsAromatherapy Bath SaltsBooks on Herbal Medicine Bulk Chinese Herb TeaFormulas from ChinaGreen Tea and More!Healing LinimentsIlluminations DecalsImperial Elixir GinsengLong Hay Flat FormulasMen's ProductsMiscellaneous ProductsOral Health CarePain ReliefPet HealthPorcelain Incense BurnersSanjiu Herbal ExtractsShoyeido IncenseSpecial Order Custom FormulasSports & Martial Art ProductsStarwest ExtractsWomen's Health ProductsYin Yang Sisters TeaGinseng ProductsClose-outs & Specials
Customer CommentsProduct IndexFormula Quick ReferenceProduct TestimonialsRoot Rap - Herb BlogTrack UPS ShipmentsPoliciesBooks We are Mentioned InSecrets of Iron PalmHadady's Health SecretsCalifornia Prop 65 InfoLinks
Home > Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy. Any and all information collected on this site is kept strictly confidential and is not sold or disclosed to third parties or reused without your permission. Any information you give to us will be held with care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to.
This website places cookies on your computer for the sole purpose of loading the site faster when you return to this website. No personal information is collected with these cookies. Microsoft is used for advertising services on the Merchant Site. Users may choose to not participate in Microsoft’s personalized advertising services, by going to the Microsoft Online Privacy Statement at http://privacy.microsoft.com where users may “opt out” of such personalized advertising services. Microsoft may retain and use user data collected in connection with the Program subject to the terms of the Microsoft Online Privacy Statement (available at http://privacy.microsoft.com). Other than as provided in the Microsoft Online Privacy Statement, Microsoft will not disclose to any third parties any user data collected in connection with the Program in a manner that contains or reveals any personally-identifiable information.
Your cart is empty.
Email Address:
Home | About Us | Contact Us | My Account | Shipping Policy | Return Policy | Privacy Policy | Sitemap | Cart Help
© 2020East Earth Trade Winds Chinese Herb Store
